Really? That means he's either
embarrassed by the relationship...
(Beverley:)...or he doesn't care enough
about his mother to tell her he's in one.
(Beverley:)Either way,
one of us should be insulted.
(Penny:)-Well, let's go find out who.
-You go get a taxi.
(Beverley:)I'm gonna slip my business card
into that busboy's back pocket...
(Beverley:)...cupping his firm right buttock
as I do so.
(Sheldon:)-Leonard?
-Sonny boy.
(Penny:)Get out here!
Your mommy wants to talk to you!
(Leonard:)What the hell is going on?
[IN SINGSONG TONE]
You're in trouble.
(Leonard:)Why didn't you tell me
you were tapping my homegirl?
(Beverley:)-Did I say that right?
-Yeah. Not bad, not bad.
(Leonard:)Are you guys drunk?
(Beverley:)Well, I hope so. Otherwise, why would
we have stopped at Del Taco?